let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "'He works in a bank' <br> She said _____________________________",
    answer: "That he worked in a bank",
    options: [
      "He worked in a bank",
      "That he worked in a bank",
      "Which he worked in a bank",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "'We went out last night'<br> She told me_____________________________",
    answer: "That they went (had gone) out last night (the night before).",
    options: [
      "That they went (had gone) out last night (the night before).",
      "They went (had gone) out last night (the night before).",
      "Which they went (had gone) out last night (the night before).",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "'I’m coming!' <br> She said_____________________________",
    answer: "That she was coming.",
    options: [
      "Which she was coming.",
      "She was coming.",
      "May she was coming.",
      "That she was coming."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "'I was waiting for the bus when he arrived' <br> She told me_____________________________",
    answer: "That she had been waiting for the bus when he arrived.",
    options: [
      "That she had been waiting for the bus when he arrived.",
      "She had been waiting for the bus when he arrived.",
      "Which she had been waiting for the bus when he arrived.",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "'I’d never been there before' <br> She said_____________________________",
    answer: "That she had never been there before.",
    options: [
      "She had never been there before.",
      "Which she had never been there before.",
      "Could she had never been there before.",
      "That she had never been there before."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "'I didn’t go to the party' <br> She told me_____________________________",
    answer: "That she didn't go (hadn't gone) to the party.",
    options: [
      "She didn't go (hadn't gone) to the party.",
      "Which she didn't go (hadn't gone) to the party.",
      "That she didn't go (hadn't gone) to the party.",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "'Lucy’ll come later' <br> She said_____________________________",
    answer: "That Lucy would come later.",
    options: [
      "Lucy would come later.",
      "Which Lucy would come later.",
      "That Lucy would come later.",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "'He hasn’t eaten breakfast' <br> She told me_____________________________",
    answer: "That he hadn't eaten breakfast.",
    options: [
      "He hadn't eaten breakfast.",
      "Which he hadn't eaten breakfast.",
      "That he hadn't eaten breakfast.",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "'I can help you tomorrow' <br> She said_____________________________",
    answer: "That she could help me tomorrow.",
    options: [
      "That she could help me tomorrow.",
      "She could help me tomorrow.",
      "All of above",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "'You should go to bed early' <br> She told me_____________________________",
    answer: "That I should go to bed early.",
    options: [
      "Which I should go to bed early.",
      "I should go to bed early.",
      "That I should go to bed early.",
      "None of above"
    ]
  },
];